const QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: "Which team (that had the best record in the NBA) did the 'We Believe' 2006-07 Warriors squad beat in the first round of the playoffs that year?",
        choices: [
            'Los Angeles Lakers',
            'Dallas Mavericks',
            'San Antonio Spurs',
            'Houston Rockets'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        explanation: 'The Warriors pulled off the upset 4 games to 2 against the Dallas Mavericks.'
    },
    {
        question: "What year did the Warriors win their first NBA championship after moving to Golden State?",
        choices: [
            '1975',
            '1986',
            '1969',
            '1982'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        explanation: 'The Warriors, led by Rick Barry, swept the Washington Bullets on their way to the title in 1975.'
    },
    {
        question: "How many threes did Stephen Curry make when he broke the single season record in 2016?",
        choices: [
            '399',
            '408',
            '405',
            '402'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        explanation: 'Chef Curry averaged an astonishing 5.1 threes per game that season for a total of 402.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which coach has the most all time wins with the franchise?",
        choices: [
            'Al Attles',
            'Steve Kerr',
            'Don Nelson',
            'Mark Jackson'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        explanation: 'Al Attles accumulated 557 wins with the team from 1970 to 1983.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which member of the 2017-18 roster was able to walk at seven months and read by the age of three? ",
        choices: [
            'Draymond Green',
            'Kevon Looney',
            'Shaun Livingston',
            'Andre Iguodala'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        explanation: 'Shaun Livingston was quite the child prodigy.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which player was suspended by the league for choking head coach PJ Carlesimo?",
        choices: [
            'Chris Webber',
            'Gilbert Arenas',
            'Mitch Richmond',
            'Latrell Sprewell'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        explanation: 'Latrell Sprewell was later traded to the New York Knicks because of this incident.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which player's jersey has not been retired by the organization?",
        choices: [
            'Chris Mullin (17)',
            'Eric "Sleepy" Floyd (21)',
            'Tom Meschery (14)',
            'Nate Thurmond (42)'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        explanation: 'Although he as a terrific player, Sleepy Floyd\'s jersey was never retired by the team.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which bridge is featured on the Warriors' logo?",
        choices: [
            'Golden Gate Bridge',
            'Bay Bridge',
            'San Mateo Bridge',
            'San Rafael Bridge'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        explanation: 'The Bay Bridge links the Warriors former home, San Francisco, with their present home, Oakland, and was featured on theiy jersey in 1970.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which opposing player threw a trash can at the wall and left a hole near the Warriors' locker room?",
        choices: [
            'Dirk Nowitzki',
            'Kobe Bryant',
            'Shaquille O\'Neal',
            'Lebron James'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        explanation: 'Dirk Nowitzki put this hole in the wall after his favored Mavericks were upset by the Warriors in 2007.'
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the only Golden State Warrior to win the slam dunk contest?",
        choices: [
            'Monta Ellis',
            'Mickael Pietrus',
            'Jason Richardson',
            'Baron Davis'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        explanation: 'J-Rich won this title back to back in 2002 and 2003.'
    }
]